(this["webpackJsonprosetta-app"]=this["webpackJsonprosetta-app"]||[]).push([[0],[,,,,,,,function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},,,,,,,,function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){},function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var s=n(0),r=n(1),c=n.n(r),a=n(10),i=n.n(a),o=(n(16),n(3)),u=n(4),j=n(6),l=n(5),d=(n(17),n(7),n(2));n(8);function x(){var e=[{questionText:"What greeting is appropriate in the morning?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Goodbye",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Good night",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Good evening",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Good morning",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Which sentence is not correct?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"I love dogs!",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"How you are?",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"I have one brother.",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"I am hungry.",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"What is ten minus seven?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"three",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"four",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"seventeen",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"zero",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Would I be an amazing employee?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"yes.",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Absolutely",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Without a doubt",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Most definitely",isCorrect:!0}]}],t=Object(r.useState)(0),n=Object(d.a)(t,2),c=n[0],a=n[1],i=Object(r.useState)(!1),o=Object(d.a)(i,2),u=o[0],j=o[1],l=Object(r.useState)(0),x=Object(d.a)(l,2),b=x[0],O=x[1];return Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"quiz",children:u?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:["You scored ",b," out of ",e.length]}):Object(s.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",c+1]}),"/",e.length]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:e[c].questionText})]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[c].answerOptions.map((function(t){return Object(s.jsx)("button",{className:"answerButton",onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&O(b+1);var n=c+1;n<e.length?a(n):j(!0)}(t.isCorrect)},children:t.answerText})}))})]})})}var b=function(e){Object(j.a)(n,e);var t=Object(l.a)(n);function n(){return Object(o.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(s.jsx)("h1",{children:"Hello World!"}),Object(s.jsx)("p",{className:"intro",children:"My name is Joshua Gaucin, I am a Software Developer with a passion for languages, be it human or computer. Test your skills in English, Japanese, Spanish, and Arabic."}),Object(s.jsx)("p",{children:"Please enjoy this fun quiz!"}),Object(s.jsx)(x,{})]})}}]),n}(c.a.Component);n(18);function O(){var e=[{questionText:"\u0645\u0627\u0647\u064a \u062a\u062d\u064a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d\u0629\u061f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0627\u0644\u0649 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u0642\u0627\u0621",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u0644\u064a\u0644\u0629 \u0633\u0639\u064a\u062f\u0629",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u0645\u0633\u0627\u0621 \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u0635\u0628\u0627\u062d \u0627\u0644\u062e\u064a\u0631",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"\u0645\u0627 \u0647\u064a \u0627\u0644\u062c\u0645\u0644\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u063a\u064a\u0631 \u0635\u062d\u064a\u062d\u0629",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0627\u062d\u0628 \u0627\u0644\u0643\u0644\u0627\u0628",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u062d\u0627\u0644\u0643 \u0643\u064a\u0641\u061f",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u0639\u0646\u062f\u064a \u0623\u062e \u0648\u0627\u062d\u062f",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u0623\u0646\u0627 \u062c\u0627\u0626\u0639",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:" \u0639\u0634\u0631\u0629 \u0646\u0627\u0642\u0635 \u0633\u0628\u0639\u0629 \u062a\u0633\u0627\u0648\u064a ",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u062b\u0644\u0627\u062b\u0629",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u0627\u0631\u0628\u0639\u0629",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u0633\u0628\u0639\u0629 \u0639\u0634\u0631\u0629",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u0635\u0641\u0631",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"\u0647\u0644 \u0633\u0623\u0643\u0648\u0646 \u0639\u0627\u0645\u0644 \u062c\u064a\u062f\u061f",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u0646\u0639\u0645",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u0628\u0625\u0637\u0644\u0627\u0642",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u0628\u0643\u0644 \u062a\u0623\u0643\u064a\u062f",isCorrect:!0}]}],t=Object(r.useState)(0),n=Object(d.a)(t,2),c=n[0],a=n[1],i=Object(r.useState)(!1),o=Object(d.a)(i,2),u=o[0],j=o[1],l=Object(r.useState)(0),x=Object(d.a)(l,2),b=x[0],O=x[1];return Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"quiz",children:u?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:[e.length," \u0644\u0642\u062f \u0623\u062d\u0631\u0632\u062a ",b," \u0645\u0646"]}):Object(s.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("span",{children:["\u0633\u0624\u0627\u0644 ",c+1]}),"/",e.length]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:e[c].questionText})]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[c].answerOptions.map((function(t){return Object(s.jsx)("button",{className:"answerButton",onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&O(b+1);var n=c+1;n<e.length?a(n):j(!0)}(t.isCorrect)},children:t.answerText})}))})]})})}var h=function(e){Object(j.a)(n,e);var t=Object(l.a)(n);function n(){return Object(o.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(s.jsx)("h1",{children:"\u0627\u0647\u0644\u0627 \u064a\u0627 \u0639\u0627\u0644\u0645"}),Object(s.jsx)("p",{className:"intro",children:"\u0627\u0647\u0644\u0627 \u0628\u0643\u0645 \u0641\u064a \u062a\u0639\u0644\u0645 \u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0625\u0646\u0633\u0627\u0646 \u0648\u0627\u0644\u062d\u0627\u0633\u0648\u0628 \u0628\u0643\u0648\u0646\u064a \u0645\u0647\u0646\u062f\u0633 \u0641\u064a \u062a\u062f\u0631\u064a\u0633 \u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a \u0648\u062e\u0635\u0648\u0635\u0627 \u0644\u062f\u0649 \u0631\u0648\u0633\u064a\u0637\u0627 \u0633\u062a\u0648\u0646 \u0643\u0623\u0646\u0647 \u062d\u0644\u0645 \u064a\u062a\u062d\u0642\u0642 \u0628\u0627\u0644\u0646\u0633\u0628\u0629 \u0644\u064a"}),Object(s.jsx)("p",{children:"\u0645\u0646 \u0641\u0636\u0644\u0643\u0645 \u062a\u0645\u062a\u0639 \u0628\u0647\u0630\u0627 \u0627\u0644\u0627\u0645\u062a\u062d\u0627\u0646 \u0627\u0644\u0645\u0645\u062a\u0639"}),Object(s.jsx)(O,{})]})}}]),n}(c.a.Component);n(19);function w(){var e=[{questionText:"\u671d\u306f\u3069\u3093\u306a\u6328\u62f6\u304c\u3044\u3044\u3067\u3059\u304b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u3055\u3088\u3046\u306a\u3089",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u304a\u3084\u3059\u307f\u306a\u3055\u3044",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u3053\u3093\u3070\u3093\u306f",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u304a\u306f\u3088\u3046\u3054\u3056\u3044\u307e\u3059\u3002",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"\u3069\u306e\u6587\u304c\u6b63\u3057\u304f\u3042\u308a\u307e\u305b\u3093\u304c",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u3044\u306c\u304c\u5927\u597d\u304d\u3067\u3059\u3088",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u3067\u3059\u304b\u5143\u6c17",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u5144\u5f1f\u304c\u3072\u3068\u308a\u3044\u307e\u3059.",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u304a\u8179\u304c\u7a7a\u3044\u305f",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"\u5341\u30de\u30a4\u30ca\u30b9\u4e03\u306e\u7d50\u679c\u306f\u4f55\u3067\u3059\u304b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u4e09",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u56db",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u5341\u4e03",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"\u3007",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"\u7d20\u6674\u3089\u3057\u3044\u5f93\u696d\u54e1\u306b\u306a\u308a\u307e\u3059\u304b",answerOptions:[{answerText:"\u306f\u3044.",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u7d76\u5bfe\u306b",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u9593\u9055\u3044\u306a\u304f",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"\u78ba\u5b9f\u306b",isCorrect:!0}]}],t=Object(r.useState)(0),n=Object(d.a)(t,2),c=n[0],a=n[1],i=Object(r.useState)(!1),o=Object(d.a)(i,2),u=o[0],j=o[1],l=Object(r.useState)(0),x=Object(d.a)(l,2),b=x[0],O=x[1];return Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"quiz",children:u?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:["\u5f97\u70b9\u3057\u305f\u3000",b," \u304b\u3089 ",e.length]}):Object(s.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("span",{children:["\u3000\u8cea\u554f\u3000",c+1]}),"/",e.length]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:e[c].questionText})]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[c].answerOptions.map((function(t){return Object(s.jsx)("button",{className:"answerButton",onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&O(b+1);var n=c+1;n<e.length?a(n):j(!0)}(t.isCorrect)},children:t.answerText})}))})]})})}var p=function(e){Object(j.a)(n,e);var t=Object(l.a)(n);function n(){return Object(o.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(s.jsx)("h1",{children:"\u3053\u3093\u306b\u3061\u306f\u4e16\u754c\uff01"}),Object(s.jsx)("p",{className:"intro",children:"\u79c1\u306e\u540d\u524d\u306f\u30b8\u30e7\u30b7\u30e5\u30a2\u30ac\u30a6\u30b7\u30a2\u30f3\u3067\u3059\u3002\u79c1\u306f\u30bd\u30d5\u30c8\u30a6\u30a7\u30a2\u30a8\u30f3\u30b8\u30cb\u30a2\u3067\u3001\u8a9e\u5b66\u3001\u4eba\u9593\u3001\u30b3\u30f3\u30d4\u30e5\u30fc\u30bf\u30fc\u304c\u5927\u597d\u304d\u3067\u3059\u3002 \u82f1\u8a9e\u3067\u3042\u306a\u305f\u306e\u30b9\u30ad\u30eb\u3092\u30c6\u30b9\u30c8\u3057\u3001 \u65e5\u672c\u8a9e\u3001\u30b9\u30da\u30a4\u30f3\u8a9e\u3001\u30a2\u30e9\u30d3\u30a2\u8a9e"}),Object(s.jsx)("p",{children:"\u3053\u306e\u697d\u3057\u3044\u30af\u30a4\u30ba\u3092\u304a\u697d\u3057\u307f\u304f\u3060\u3055\u3044"}),Object(s.jsx)(w,{})]})}}]),n}(c.a.Component);n(20),n(21),n(22);function T(){var e=[{questionText:"Que saludo es apropiado para la ma\xf1ana?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Adi\xf3s",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Buenas noches",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Buena noches\u3000",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Buenos d\xedas",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"Que frase es incorrecto?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Yo amo los perros",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Est\xe1s c\xf3mo ",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Tengo un hermano",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Tengo hambre",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Que es diez menos siete?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Tres",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Quatoro",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Diecisiete",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Cero",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"Yo seria un excelente empleado?",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Si",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Absoltamente",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Sin ninguna duda",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Definitivamente",isCorrect:!0}]}],t=Object(r.useState)(0),n=Object(d.a)(t,2),c=n[0],a=n[1],i=Object(r.useState)(!1),o=Object(d.a)(i,2),u=o[0],j=o[1],l=Object(r.useState)(0),x=Object(d.a)(l,2),b=x[0],O=x[1];return Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"quiz",children:u?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:["Tu puntuacion ",b," fuera de ",e.length]}):Object(s.jsxs)(s.Fragment,{children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(s.jsxs)("span",{children:["Pregunta\u3000",c+1]}),"/",e.length]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",children:e[c].questionText})]}),Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[c].answerOptions.map((function(t){return Object(s.jsx)("button",{className:"answerButton",onClick:function(){return function(t){t&&O(b+1);var n=c+1;n<e.length?a(n):j(!0)}(t.isCorrect)},children:t.answerText})}))})]})})}var C=function(e){Object(j.a)(n,e);var t=Object(l.a)(n);function n(){return Object(o.a)(this,n),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){return Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(s.jsx)("h1",{children:"Hola Mundo"}),Object(s.jsx)("p",{className:"intro",children:"Mi nombre es Joshua Gaucin, soy un ingeniero de softwares apasionado de los idiomas, ya sean de computadora o humanos. Pon a prueba tus habilidades en ingl\xe9s, Japon\xe9s, espa\xf1ol y \xe1rabe.."}),Object(s.jsx)("p",{children:"Por favor disfruta este divertido cuestionario"}),Object(s.jsx)(T,{})]})}}]),n}(c.a.Component),g=function(e){Object(j.a)(n,e);var t=Object(l.a)(n);function n(){var e;return Object(o.a)(this,n),(e=t.call(this)).state={language:"en"},e}return Object(u.a)(n,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return"en"===this.state.language?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{className:"container",children:[Object(s.jsx)(b,{}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{class:"dropdown",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{class:"dropbtn",children:"Languages"}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{class:"dropdown-content",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"arabic"})},children:"\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"es"})},children:"Espa\xf1ol"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"jap"})},children:"\u65e5\u672c\u8a9e"})]})]})]}):"jap"===this.state.language?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(s.jsx)(p,{}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{class:"dropdown",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{class:"dropbtn",children:"\u8a00\u8a9e"}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{class:"dropdown-content",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"arabic"})},children:"\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"en"})},children:"English"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"es"})},children:"Espa\xf1ol"})]})]})]}):"es"===this.state.language?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(s.jsx)(C,{}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{class:"dropdown",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{class:"dropbtn",children:"Idiomas"}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{class:"dropdown-content",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"en"})},children:"English"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"arabic"})},children:"\u0627\u0644\u0644\u063a\u0629 \u0627\u0644\u0639\u0631\u0628\u064a\u0629"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"jap"})},children:"\u65e5\u672c\u8a9e"})]})]})]}):"arabic"===this.state.language?Object(s.jsxs)("div",{children:[Object(s.jsx)(h,{}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{class:"dropdown",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{class:"dropbtn",children:"\u0644\u063a\u0627\u062a"}),Object(s.jsxs)("div",{class:"dropdown-content",children:[Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"en"})},children:"English"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"es"})},children:"Espa\xf1ol"}),Object(s.jsx)("button",{onClick:function(){e.setState({language:"jap"})},children:"\u65e5\u672c\u8a9e"})]})]})]}):void 0}}]),n}(c.a.Component);n(23);var v=function(){return Object(s.jsx)("div",{className:"App",children:Object(s.jsx)(g,{})})},m=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&n.e(3).then(n.bind(null,25)).then((function(t){var n=t.getCLS,s=t.getFID,r=t.getFCP,c=t.getLCP,a=t.getTTFB;n(e),s(e),r(e),c(e),a(e)}))};i.a.render(Object(s.jsx)(c.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(s.jsx)(v,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),m()}],[[24,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.c525fbba.chunk.js.map